http://youtu.be/Jwoe_CF8ozA
phungdo_vgu http://youtu.be/Jwoe_CF8ozA
JON VALVANO: Hi, I'm Jon Valvano, a professor of electrical and computer
Chào, tôi là Jon Valvano, giáo sư khoa điện và kĩ thuật
engineering here at the University of Texas at Austin.
máy tính tại ĐH Texas Austin.
I received my bachelor's and master's degree in 1977 from MIT in computer
Tôi nhận bằng cử nhân và thạc sĩ vào năm 1977 ở MIT, ngành kĩ thuật
engineering.
máy tính.
And then in 1981, I received my Ph.D. From the joint Harvard MIT program in
Rồi tới 1981, tôi học xong tiến sĩ. Trong một chương trình liên kết giữa Hardvard - MIT
medical engineering and medical physics.
kĩ thuật y học và vật lý y sinh.
I've been here at the University of Texas for 32 years, teaching and doing
Tôi đã làm việc ở ĐH Texas 32 năm, giảng dạy và
research in medical instrumentation.
nghiên cứu thiết bị y tế.
I've written five college textbooks on embedded systems, and my research
Tôi viết 5 quyển giáo trình về hệ thống nhúng, và nghiên cứu của tôi
involves analog and digital circuits, low power design, simulation, and
có mạch tương tự (analog) và kĩ thuật số thiết kế công suất thấp, mô phỏng,
medical instrumentation.
thiết bị đo y tế.
Recently, I co-founded a company called Admittance Technologies, which
Mới đây, tôi đồng sáng lập một cty tên là Admittance Technologies, nó
deploys medical devices for cardiac measurements.
triển khai thiết bị y tế cho chẩn đoán tim.
I just love to build things.
Tôi chỉ thích việc làm ra sản phẩm.
But more importantly, I just love teaching.
Nhưng quan trọng hơn, Tôi rất thích giảng dạy.